mizoramexpress.com 2010-12-19

# Privacy | Mizoram Express

[ ](http://mizoramexpress.com/wp-content/uploads/terms-of-usage1.jpg)Welcome to Mizoram Express! We appreciate your participation as citizen journalist and visitor. Our goal is to encourage writers in English from all Mizo tribes and concerned citizens to bring to light the good, the bad and the ugly from all aspects of governance to societal practices. However, in order to maintain a civil community, we require you to follow the following basic guidelines:

**Right to Delete Posts**

While we do not and cannot review every message posted by you you must agree that you are responsible for the content of your news item, comments and views. We reserve the right to delete, move or edit messages that we deem abusive, defamatory, obscene, in violation of copyright or trademark laws, or otherwise unacceptable. All posts in the ‘ME Citizen Journalist’ Section must be written in English. We reserve the right to remove the posting privileges of users who violate the standards of ME Citizen Journalist Section’s behavior at any time.

**Uploading**

You cannot upload to the Web site, or distribute or otherwise publish through it, anything that is libelous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic or abusive, or that otherwise violates any Indian law. We regret that MExpress cannot honor requests to remove posts except when such postings violate our editorial and policies.

**Graphics**

Graphics and small audio files are permitted but javascript files are not allowed.

**Noncommercial**

The ‘ME Citizen Journalist’ section can be used only in a noncommercial manner. You cannot, without the express approval of ME Team distribute or otherwise publish material containing any solicitation of funds, advertising or solicitation of goods or services.

**Spamming**

Repeatedly posting off-topic messages or “spamming” our site by posting the same message in multiple topics or otherwise deliberately disrupting our site is unacceptable behavior that may result in the user’s losing all ME Citizen Journalist’s privileges and access to our site. We reserve the right to prohibit users who in any way violate acceptable ME CJ behavior from participating. Users remain solely responsible for the content of their messages.

**Privacy Policy:**

This Privacy Policy sets out the privacy policies and practices for Mizoram Express (ME),  ****with respect to the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information in connection with ME ****. This Privacy Policy may be updated giving reasonable notice of the revised terms (including by e-mail or by posting on the Site), and this Privacy Policy may be supplemented or modified by agreements entered into between ME and an individual from time to time. In this Privacy Policy, “ **personal information** ” means any information about an identifiable individual, as further defined under applicable Indian laws.

Collection and Use of Personal Information

ME collects personal information from you when you subscribe for services or products, and may from time to time collect additional personal information in the course of providing such products and services. ME uses such personal information as is reasonably required to process your registration for the Site and to provide services and products to you.

Contact information that you provide to ME may be used to contact you in connection with the Site. For example, depending on which services you have subscribed to and which privacy preferences you have indicated to ME, we may use your contact information to provide periodic newsletters or to provide notices regarding changes to the Site or regarding new services or products.

This Site allows you to publish personal information about yourself and others, including videos and photos. By publishing your personal information on such pages, you consent to the publication of such personal information. By publishing personal information about another individual, you represent that you have, where required by applicable privacy laws, obtained the consent of such individuals to publish such information.

ME collects demographic and profile data in connection with the Site and uses such data to tailor each visitor’s experience at the Site, showing the user content in which ME thinks you might be interested, and displaying the content according to your preferences.

ME may use customer information for additional purposes that may be identified at or before the time that the information is collected.

Disclosure of Personal Information

ME may disclose personal information as follows:

  * to third party service providers and to affiliated entities in order to carry out work on behalf of ME,
  * to law enforcement agencies for the purposes of investigating fraud or other offences,
  * to legal, financial, insurance, and other advisors or in connection with the sale, reorganization, or management of all or part of its business or operations, and
  * as consented to by you from time to time, including to fulfill any other purposes that are identified when the personal information is collected.

ME will not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with your consent or as required or permitted by law.

Cookies and IP Addresses

ME uses your IP address to help identify you and your subscription, gather broad demographic information about our users, diagnose problems with our systems, and administer the Site. The Site is entitled to use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, according to your preferences, and to save your password so that you are not required to re-enter it while you use the Site.

Links

The Site contains links to other websites. ME is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Please ensure you review the privacy policies of the websites that you visit.

Security

ME protects against the loss, misuse, and alteration of personal information with security measures appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. However, it is possible that any information transmitted via the Internet may be intercepted by unknown third parties.

Opt-Out

When appropriate, users of the Site are given the opportunity to (i) opt-out of receiving communications from us, (ii) remove their personal information from our records, or (iii) elect to no longer receive services from us. If you wish to opt-out of receiving further communications, please contact ME ****by email.

Corrections/Contact

You may contact ME to modify or correct any of their personal information that is under our control. You may also direct a written complaint regarding compliance with this Privacy Policy to ME and, within a reasonable time upon receiving the written complaint, we will conduct an investigation into the matter. Within a reasonable time of concluding the investigation, ME will inform you whether the complaint will be allowed or denied. If the ME allows the complaint, we will take appropriate measure necessary to rectify the source of the complaint.

Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, ME’s privacy practices in connection with this Site, or ME’s collection, use, disclosure, or retention of your personal information in connection with this Site, please contact ME:

MExpress  
mizoramexpress@gmail.com  
India

Share this post with others:
